原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     冰岛豆腐   吃冰棒
翻译     feip   蛇蝎再续前缘栗
翻译     泽生   建峤   苏葵
校对     冰岛豆腐
时间轴     无关风粤
后期     8T
总监     冰岛豆腐
《致命女人》前情提要
Previously on Why Women Kill..
他们给我洗胃了
They pumped my stomach.
我不会出那个医药费的
I'm not paying for that.
明明打个嗝都能吐出药片救活你
Not when a good burp would've saved you.
卡尔的轻率之举我已经耳闻一段时间了
I've known for some time about Karl's indiscretions.
有天我去取干洗的衣服
I was picking up my dry cleaning,
他的车停在那里
and there was his car,
就在街对面的什么三流旅馆前面
parked across the street at some seedy motel.
你还想跟我滚床单吗
You still want to make love to me?
-是的  -我今天四点没事
- Yeah. - I'm free today at 4:00.
我们应该去哪里
Where should we go?
你是个男人了  自己想
You're a man now; figure it out.
我不会进入你的移动性窝的
There's no way I'm getting into your mobile sex den.
你看上去容光焕发
You seem, uh... energized.
是吗
Do I?
你最近是开始了新的锻炼课程吗
Have you embarked on a new exercise regimen?
我打算有空就去健身
I plan on working out as often as I can.
那天她一直不停地说
The other day, she was going on and on
她有多喜欢我的电影
about how much she liked my movie.
我们已经是开放式婚姻了
You know what? We've already got an open marriage...
我会去问她愿不愿意三人行
I'll ask her for a three-way.
如果她拒绝的话...
If she says no...
她同意了
She says yes.
天呐
Oh, my God.
你爱上她了吗
You in love with her?
你最近没有安全感
You've been insecure lately
-因为你事业不顺  -你爱上她了吗
- because of your career. - Are you in love with her?
没有
No.
你的有妇之夫有跟你说过
Has your married man ever told you
他为什么需要出轨吗
why he feels the need to cheat?
他厌倦了自己的老婆
He was bored with his wife.
这是本手册  给夫妻用的
It's a manual. For married couples.
这都是小黄图
These are dirty pictures.
都是很科学的
They're scientific.
我需要专注
I have to concentrate.
罗伯  拜托别走
Rob, please don't go.
今晚真令人尴尬
This has been an awkward night.
我必须到场
I need to make an appearance.
他们一定是重要客户
They must be important clients.
别等我
Don't wait up.
致命女人
第一季  第三集
开始很缓慢
It begins quite slowly.
一个表情
With a look.
或者一个动作
Or a gesture.
一旦接受了邀请
And once the invitation is accepted...
探戈就开始
The tango begins.
这是预见的舞
It is a dance of anticipation.
-诱惑的舞  -欲望的舞
- Seduction. - Desire.
也是爱情的舞
And love.
有人说两个人才能跳探戈
You know, some say it takes two to tango.
但有时  潜伏在黑暗中的
But sometimes, lurking in the dark...
是第三人
Is a third.
如果你要和他跳舞
Now, if you choose to dance with him,
做好应对后果的准备
be prepared to deal with the consequences.
因为激情可以变成嫉妒
For passion can turn to jealousy.
爱可以变得暴力
Love can become violent.
是的  探戈的存在是为了提醒我们
Yes. The tango exists to remind us
最伟大的爱情故事
the greatest love stories...
都以死亡收场
End in death.
跟你说下
Just a reminder,
我明天前要完成那个项目
I've got that project due tomorrow.
所以你又要加班吗
So you'll be working late again?
恐怕是的
Afraid so.
抱歉  亲爱的
Sorry, honey.
你今天有什么计划
What are your big plans for the day?
没什么有意思的
Oh, nothing interesting.
要去干洗店
Need to drop by the dry cleaners.
然后去集市买点东西
After that, I'll go to the market for some shopping.
然后也许会和一个新朋友吃午饭
And then I might have lunch with a new friend.
这是你的电话号码
This is your phone number.
既然我们成了密友了
Oh, I thought you should have it,
我想你应该知道
now that we're getting to be chums.
这样  如果你哪天
This way, if you ever need someone
需要约人去看电影
to go with you to the movies...
我可以打给你  明白
I can call you up. Got it.
我在一对恩爱夫妻那租了一间房
Now, I rent a room from a lovely couple.
妻子的名字也叫希拉
The wife's name is also Sheila.
如果你打电话  她接了的话
So, if you call and she answers...
那我就说找另一个希拉
Then I'll ask for the other Sheila.
没错  这周很忙吗
Exactly. Busy this week?
我安排挺松的  除了今晚
Uh, my schedule is pretty open, except for tonight.
我有约会
I have a date.
和你的有妇之夫
With your married man?
他完成了一个大项目  为了庆祝
He finished some big project at work. To celebrate,
他在一个高级夜店给我们定了位子
he got us reservations at this really fancy night club.
他要带你出去
He's taking you out?
当众
In public?
第一次  就像是真的男友一样
For the first time. It's like an actual boyfriend.
是不是很棒
Isn't that nice?
你在笑什么
What are you smiling about?
这事的荒谬
Oh, the absurdity of it all.
我要在餐车上
I'm having the best sex of my life
享受美妙性生活了
in the back of a catering van.
也许等格罗夫先生搬出去后
Well, maybe when Mr. Grove moves out,
我们可以去你的床上做
we could start doing this in your bed.
好
Yes...
说到这个
So, about that...
卡尔或许会在我家比预想中住得久一点
Karl may be staying in my home longer than we discussed.
多久  一周吗
How much longer? A week?
不止
Longer.
两周
Two weeks?
他要在我女儿婚礼之后才会走
He won't be leaving until after my daughter's wedding.
那还要两个月啊
That's two months away.
我不介意在车上做
Well, I don't mind the van.
不  那不是重点
No, that's-that's not the point.
萨蒙妮  他背着你和男人偷情
Simone, he cheated on you with men.
你为什么不马上赶他走
Why would you let him stay for five more seconds?
我也想赶他走
Well, I tried to throw him out.
-他不走吗  -他说如果我赶他走
- And he wouldn't go? - He said that if I made him leave,
他就要告诉我所有朋友他是同性恋
he would tell all my friends he was gay
在婚礼前让我丢脸
and embarrass me before the wedding.
所以他是在威胁你
So he's threatening you?
不  只是小小的勒索
No, it's just a little light blackmail.
好吧  我来搞定这件事
All right. I'll take care of this.
什么意思
What does that mean?
没什么  我要让他明白他在犯错
Nothing. I'm just gonna convince him that he's making a mistake.
真可爱
That's adorable.
我是认真的
Hey, I'm serious.
请让我帮你
Please, let me help.
当然不行
Absolutely not.
我不会伤他太重
I'm not gonna break any bones.
我只会让他吃点苦头
I'm just gonna bend some stuff.
汤米  你觉得如果你去揍我丈夫
Tommy, how do you expect our secret affair to remain secret
被警察抓了
once you've been arrested by the police
我们的私情还怎么藏得住
for beating up my husband?
我只是随便说说
I was just spitballing.
我很感谢你的热情
Well, I appreciate the passion,
但还是把它留在车里吧
but save it for the van.
我还是想找个晚上在一条小黑巷里单独会会卡尔
I'd still love to meet Karl alone in a dark alley some night.
当心
Careful.
他可能会很喜欢那样呢
He might enjoy that.
好的  不  我明白
Yes. Um, no, I understand,
只是我已经看了两遍证词
it's just that I've been through the deposition twice
没有找到任何有用的东西
and I couldn't find anything useful.
伊莱
Eli.
好
Yes.
我会再看一遍的
I will check again.
没问题
Sure.
那是什么
What's that?
今早买的  很不错吧
Got it this morning. It's pretty sweet, right?
你不是已经有把吉他了吗
Uh, don't you already have a guitar?
是  不  亲爱的  这是把贝斯
Yeah, no, honey, this is a bass.
有五根弦  听起来完全不一样  你听
Five strings, it sounds totally different. Check it out.
-很酷  -是啊
- Very cool. - Yeah.
-你去厨房吗  -嗯
- Oh, are you going to the kitchen? - Yeah.
能帮我拿杯汽水吗
Could you grab me a soda?
好
Sure.
里面冻成碎冰的
With the, the crushy ice?
爱你
Love you.
你听说那个大消息了吗
Did you hear the big news?
伊莱买了把贝斯
Eli bought a bass.
听见了
Oh, I heard.
他觉得这能帮他突破写作瓶颈
He thinks it's gonna help him work through his writer's block.
很好  他也是因为这个理由买了那把吉他
Great. That's how he ended up with his other guitar,
那台游戏机和椭圆机
the Xbox and the elliptical.
明白了
Got it.
你今天过得怎么样
So, how was your day?
忙死了  我连午饭都没机会吃
It was crazy busy. I didn't even get a chance to eat lunch.
天呐  你一定要尝尝这个
Oh, God, you have to try this.
给
Here.
很烫  小心
It's hot. Careful.
-太好吃了  -很好吃吧
- That's amazing. - It's good, right?
是的  所以伊莱今天有写了什么吗
Yeah. So, did Eli get any work done today?
我不知道  我出去办事了
I'm not sure. I was running errands.
-你怎么不问他  -不了
- Why don't you ask him? - No.
如果我问伊莱  "你写了什么吗"
If I ask Eli, "Did you get any writing done?"
在他听来我只是在不停地叨叨
what he hears is, "Nag, nag, nag, nag, nag."
我什么都不会说  表示支持就好了
I'm just gonna say nothing and be supportive.
这就是我支持的微笑  你觉得怎么样
This is my supportive smile. Tell me what you think.
很可怕
It's terrifying.
我有个主意
Hey, I have an idea.
晚饭后  我们去跳舞吧
After dinner, let's go dancing.
-今晚吗  -嗯  银湖新开了一家夜店
- Tonight? - Yeah. There's this new club in Silver Lake
我超想去看看
I've been dying to check out.
我还有很多文件要看
I have a lot of reading to do for work.
拜托
Oh, come on.
你太紧绷了  我都记不起
You've been so stressed, and I can't remember
上次我们一起去跳舞是什么时候了
the last time we went dancing together.
可以来点私人时间  就我和你
I could use some alone time, just you and me.
真的吗
Really?
我们可以去泡夜店了
So we can go clubbing?
-泡夜店  -伊莱
- Clubbing? - Eli.
你不是在弹贝斯吗
Thought you were playing your bass.
我以为你会帮我拿瓶汽水
Thought you were grabbing me a soda.
我正准备拿
I was getting to it.
所以你们要去夜店
So you guys are going clubbing, huh?
是的
Yeah. Yeah, we are.
好吧  我也去
All right. I'm in.
伊莱  你又不跳舞
Eli, you don't dance.
我跳舞的  以我自己的方式
I dance. In my way.
你跳起舞来  大家都要被你干扰了
When you dance, you're in everyone's way.
怎么  你们真的不想我去吗
What? You guys really don't want me to come?
不  不  不
No. No, no, no.
我们很乐意你来  对吗
We'd love for you to come. Right?
当然
Absolutely.
笑得真诡异
Creepy smile.
卡尔
Karl?
她回来了
There she is.
娜奥米
Naomi.
我们有约吗
Did we have plans?
不是  我只是想问你个问题
No, I just popped in with a question.
卡尔说你去了邮局
Karl said you went to the post office,
所以我就等你回来
and so I waited.
等了一个小时
For an hour.
是的  我们得谈谈慈善晚会的娱乐活动
Yes. We need to talk about the entertainment for the benefit.
慈善晚会
Benefit.
为烧伤患者举办的
For the burn victims.
天呐
Oh, my God.
我完全忘记这事了
I forgot all about it.
萨蒙妮  你可是负责装饰的
Simone, you're in charge of the decorations.
没关系  我几周前已经买好东西了
It's fine. I ordered everything weeks ago.
因为最近的事情我有点分心
My mind's been elsewhere because of recent events.
你的保留节目还来吗
Are you still up for your number?
萨蒙妮答应过你们会重现
Simone promised the two of you would reprise your dance.
你们在乡村俱乐部才艺秀上的舞蹈
From the country club's talent show.
是吗
Oh, did she?
考虑到最近的事  我不确定还想不想跳
I'm not sure I'm up for it now, given recent events.
如果你们不表演的话
Well, if you don't do something,
艾达·福特扬言要唱歌剧
Ida Ford is threatening to sing opera.
亲爱的  难道火灾受害者受的罪还不够多吗
Oh, darling. Haven't the burn victims suffered enough?
好吧
All right.
我们会表演的
We'll perform.
那就好
I'm so glad.
记着
And remember:
不管你何时想倾诉何事
if you ever need to talk about anything,
我一直都在
I am always here.
是  你确实一直都在我家
Yes. You certainly seem to be.
你为什么让她进来
Why did you let her inside?
我才是该生气的那个
I'm the one who should be miffed.
你为什么不告诉我娜奥米在汽车旅馆看到了我的车
Why didn't you tell me Naomi saw my car at a motel?
万幸她只看到了你的车
We're lucky that's all she saw.
如果她知道你隐瞒身份和陌生男人约炮
If she knew you were having anonymous sex with strange men...
我从未隐瞒过身份
It was never anonymous.
而且当中只有几个是陌生人
And only a few of them were strange.
我才不要听你这破笑话
I am not the audience for that joke.
-你在干什么  -离慈善晚会只有两天了
- What are you doing? - Benefit's in two days.
我们需要排练
We need to rehearse.
我当时在想什么
Ugh, what was I thinking?
我没法和你跳舞  我还生着气呢
I can't dance with you, I'm still furious.
当我们成为全场焦点
You'll forget all about that
被掌声淹没
when we're the center of attention,
你会把这一切都忘得一干二净
drowning in applause.
不要再试图用你的魅力赢回我的心
Stop trying to charm your way back into my heart.
没用的
It won't work.
你瞧  我觉得是你忘记
Now, you see, I think you've forgotten
我们在一起时有多开心
how much fun we have together.
我誓要让你记起
And I am determined to remind you.
你为什么要这么努力地挽留我
Why are you trying so hard to hold onto me?
因为我爱你  我的宝贝
Because I love you, my darling.
恐怕那还不够
Well, I'm not sure that's enough.
那你听听这一句
Well, try this one beside.
我其实还挺喜欢你
I actually like you.
你有几任丈夫能说这话
How many of your husbands can say that?
谢了
Oh, hey. Ooh, thanks.
糟了
Oh, crap.
什么  怎么回事
What? What's wrong?
我好像看到我的经纪人了
I think I just saw my agent.
拉马尔在这儿  你怎么不去打个招呼
Lamar's here? Why don't you go say hi?
算了  他只会不停地催我
No, he's just gonna give me a hard time
交剧本
about finishing the script.
有个简单的办法可以摆脱他
There's an easy way to get him off your back.
-什么办法  -写完你的剧本
- What's that? - Finish your script.
就是因为这种态度
This kind of attitude is
我才会把你当做我前妻介绍给大家
why I introduce you to people as my first wife.
你真逗
Yeah, that's funny.
一切还好吗
Is everything okay?
还好  我现在只想和你跳舞
Yeah. I just really want to dance with you right now.
-好啊  那就跳吧  -好的
- Yeah, let's do it. - Okay.
-来吧  -洁德
- Come on. - Jade!
我的天
Oh, my God!
薇沙  我的天呐
Wischa! Oh, my God!
她刚才是说"薇沙"吗
Did she say "Wischa"?
-是的吧  -二位
- I think so. - You guys.
这是我的朋友  薇珞和米沙
These are my friends, Willow and Mischa.
薇沙  我懂了
Wischa. Ah, I get it.
这是泰勒和伊莱
This is, uh, Taylor and Eli.
你们是怎么认识洁德的
How do you two know Jade?
我们去年遇到她
We met her last year.
完全是一见钟情
Oh, and it was love at first sight.
我的天  你们嘴好甜
Oh, my God, you guys!
姐妹  你看起来太他妈赞了
Girl, you look fucking amazing.
她什么时候不他妈赞啊
Mmm, when fucking doesn't she?
从他妈没有过
Fucking never.
我感觉我们不是洁德的第一次三人行
I'm getting the feeling that we weren't Jade's first threesome.
我不明白  你为什么想要
I don't get it. Why would you want to
和这个淫妇做朋友
start palling around with this tramp?
因为我想阻止她继续见我的丈夫
Because I want to stop her from seeing my husband.
在里亚托给她买爆米花算什么
And how is buying her popcorn at the Rialto
阻止她的手段
gonna make that happen?
我在努力建立信任
I'm trying to establish trust.
如果一个陌生人走过来  说你的裙子很丑
If a stranger came up and said your dress was ugly,
你会怎么说
what would you say?
我会说滚开
I'd say fuck off.
但是如果一位好友温柔地暗示
But if a dear friend gently suggested
橘色不太适合你呢
orange is not your best color?
我会把裙子扔掉
I'd get rid of the dress.
如果我要说服艾普尔
If I'm to convince April
和一个已婚男人约会对她没好处
it's not in her best interest to date a married man,
首先我必须成为她的闺蜜
first I must become her confidant.
她的情感顾问
Her close advisor.
懂了
Okay.
那这段新友谊何时开启
So when does this new friendship begin to blossom?
今晚
Tonight.
我以为罗伯今晚要带她去俱乐部
I thought Rob was taking her to the club tonight.
你当真以为我会坐视不管吗
Do you honestly think I'm going to let that happen?
你还好吗
You all right?
-不  我很紧张  -为什么
- No, I'm nervous. - Why?
我们认识的所有人今晚都会在这里
Everyone we know will be in this room tonight.
你已惊艳过他们无数次
You've dazzled them all a hundred times.
因为我知道他们有多嫉妒我
Because I knew how much they envied me.
如果他们知道真相  定会当面嘲笑我
They'd laugh in my face if they knew the truth about us.
我有个建议  不要告诉他们
Here's a thought. Don't tell them.
大家终究会琢磨出来的
People will be able to figure it out.
你真的以为我们是这里唯一一对
Do you honestly believe we're the only couple here
不加伪装的夫妇吗
pretending to be something that we're not?
-对  -相信我
- No. - Trust me,
今晚这里的每一个女子
there is not a woman here tonight
如果有你一半漂亮的话  都会愿意
who wouldn't trade all of her problems for yours
用她自己所有的难题
if she looked half as beautiful
来跟你交换位置
as you do right now.
但是如果一切都是谎言的话
But what good is other people's envy
别人的嫉妒又有什么用呢
if it's all based on a lie?
我不确定
I'm not sure.
我们去一探究竟吧
Let's find out.
萨蒙妮  你简直美呆了
Simone! You look stunning.
你看上去像个少女
And you look like a teenager.
你的皮肤怎会如此柔软
How do you get your skin so soft?
是一种化学换肤术
It's called a chemical peel.
我知道  再弄一次她就变成歌剧魅影了
I know. One more and she'll be the Phantom of the Opera.
-萨蒙妮  -亲爱的  你好  巴克利
- Simone! - Darling. Hello, Barclay.
桑迪  你从戒瘾所出来了
Sandy, you're out of rehab.
别担心  我会回去的
Don't worry, I'll be back.
-或许我该去找咱们的桌子  -没必要
- Maybe I should go and find our table. - No need.
我已经安排我们坐在这里了
I've arranged for us all to sit here.
一起吗  有意思
Together? What fun.
我想现在去吧台一下比较好
I think this is a good time to find the bar.
酒马上来  萨蒙妮
Liquor's on it's way, Simone,
由整个派对上最可爱的侍应生端给你
brought to you by the most adorable waiter at the party.
喝红酒吗  格罗夫太太
Wine, Mrs. Grove?
汤米
Tommy.
你是我们的侍应生吗
You're our waiter?
没错  格罗夫太太
Yes, Mrs. Grove.
格罗夫先生
Mr. Grove.
你好
Hello.
走吗  亲爱的
Shall we, darling?
那么米沙  你们是做什么的
So, Mischa, what do you guys do for a living?
我们是网红
Oh, uh, we're influencers.
网红
Influencers?
在Instagram上
On Instagram.
我们挺有名的
We're sort of famous.
是吗
Are you?
对  账号名叫处处有内衣
Yeah, it's called @UnderwearEverywhere.
那些内衣品牌给我们一大笔钱
All these underwear brands pay us stupid money
上传穿着他们产品的照片
to post pictures wearing their stuff.
去全世界各个著名地标建筑打卡
At famous landmarks, like, all over the world.
你看
Yo, check it.
泰姬陵的管理人员也不介意吗
And the Taj Mahal people, they were okay with that?
我们快进快出
Ah, we were in and out lickety-split.
玩得可开心了
We had the best time.
我们很想你  小洁德
We've missed you, little Jade.
我也很想你们
Oh, I missed you.
你们要在这里待多久
So, um, how long are you guys here?
我们明晚去威尼斯
We leave tomorrow night for Venice.
-不是吧  -这么快
- No. - Oh, so soon.
真可惜
Oh, that sucks.
我还希望能多跟你们待一阵呢
I was hoping I'd have more time to hang out with you guys.
是啊  真可惜
Yeah, it sucks.
-等等  米沙  -怎么
- Wait, Mischa. - What?
我有个好主意
I just had an idea.
我知道你在想什么  简直太聪明了
I know what you're thinking, and it's fucking brilliant.
你在想什么
What are you thinking?
明天跟我们一起去威尼斯吧
Come with us to Venice tomorrow.
-天哪  -明天  真的吗
- Oh, my God. - Tomorrow? Really?
对啊  会很好玩的
Yeah, it would be so much fun.
这个...
Well...
她没有机票啊
She doesn't have a plane ticket.
我们的助理可以搞定
Our assistant can take care of that.
-你们还有助理吗  -对
- You guys have an assistant? - Yeah.
各位  拜托  这么急
Guys, come on, it's such short notice.
机票钱会很贵的
That'll cost a fortune.
拜托  我们里程数超多的
Oh, please, we've got tons of miles.
-真的吗  -对
- Really? - Yeah.
你有能用的护照吗
Do you have a current passport?
我想是的
I think so, yeah.
天哪
Oh, my God.
等等
Um, hold on.
你不能一时兴起就出国
You can't just leave the country on a whim.
太没责任感了
It's irresponsible.
好吧  老妈  天哪  冷静点
Okay, Mom. Geez, calm down.
你说什么
Excuse me?
天哪
Oh, my God!
这首歌我太喜欢了
Oh... this song is my jam!
各位  来跳舞吧  快来
Guys, let's dance. Come on.
-就是  来跳舞吧  -好吧  来跳吧
- Yeah, let's dance. - All right, let's do it.
来吧  快来  兄弟
Come on. Let's go, bro.
-我  是吗  -是的
- Me? Yeah? - Yeah.
-来吧  -好吧
- Let's do it. - All right.
我要跟他去跳舞了  所以
I'm going with him. So...
我是斯坦顿
Stanton speaking.
罗伯  是我
Rob, it's me.
真是个美好的惊喜
Well, this is a nice surprise.
我无意打扰
I don't mean to bother,
但我晚上要做金枪鱼煲
but I'm making tuna casserole for dinner.
你想要加面包碎还是不加
Do you prefer bread crumbs or not?
亲爱的  我说过我今晚工作要到很晚
Honey, I told you I'm working late tonight.
是吗  是我忘了
Oh. Did I forget?
没错  我们项目的截止日期是明天上午
Yeah, our deadline for the project is tomorrow morning.
好吧
Right.
是什么项目来着
What was the name of that again?
德尔福项目
The Delphi Project.
对对  好吧
Of course. Of course, well,
那你去工作吧
I'll let you get back to work.
好了  记得不用等我
Now, remember, don't wait up.
我凌晨才能回家
I won't be home till the wee hours.
可怜的宝贝
Oh, poor baby.
你好  克莱尔
Hello, Claire.
斯坦顿太太
Mrs. Stanton.
你丈夫没跟我说你会过来
Your husband didn't tell me you were gonna stop by.
罗伯不知道我要来
Oh, Rob isn't expecting me.
这是给他的惊喜
This is something of a surprise.
我太想喝一杯咖啡了
I am desperate for a cup of coffee.
你能帮我弄一杯过来吗
Could you be so kind?
我不能离开我的办公桌
Well, I'm-I'm not supposed to leave my desk.
克莱尔  我难得开口让你帮个忙
Claire, how often do I ask you for favors?
好的  斯坦顿夫人
Sure, Mrs. Stanton.
我很快就回来
I'll be back in a jif.
不用急  亲爱的
Don't rush, dear.
慢慢来
Take your time.
你好呀
Hi there.
贝丝·安  你怎么来了
Beth Ann. What are you doing here?
我一想到你拿自动贩卖机里
I couldn't bear the thought of you
买的垃圾食品当晚餐  心里就受不了
getting your dinner from a vending machine.
天呐  你真是太贴心了
Wow, that's thoughtful.
我知道你这里是有厨房的
I know you have a kitchen around here somewhere.
你可以先放到冰箱里  等想吃了就拿出来吃
You can pop it in the fridge until you're ready to eat.
好的
Sure.
克莱尔  能稍微进来一会儿吗
Claire, can you come in here for a second?
克莱尔
Claire?
她肯定是有事离开了
Ah, she must have wandered off.
我相信她很快就会回来
I'm sure she'll be back soon.
罗伯特
Now, Robert,
我费心费力地做了这个砂锅菜
I went to all the trouble of making this casserole.
我可不希望这里面的金枪鱼坏掉
I don't want the tuna to spoil.
我去放到冰箱里
I will put it in the fridge.
德尔福项目
斯坦顿夫人  您的咖啡好了
Mrs. Stanton, here's your coffee.
你真是太贴心了
Oh, you're so sweet.
很烫  你最好等它凉了再喝
It's very hot. You might want to give it a moment to cool off.
我可没时间等  我还有好多事要做
Oh, I don't have time to wait. I have things to do.
只需要一会儿就好
Oh, it'll just take a sec.
你真是难得的人才  告诉罗伯我回家等他了
You're a treasure. Tell Rob I'll see him back home.
谁说你可以去喝咖啡了
Who said you could have a coffee break?
我真是受宠若惊
I was so flattered.
通常汤米他们公司替我的活动承办宴席的时候
Usually when Tommy's company caters one of my events,
他都拒绝侍奉我
he refuses to wait on me.
但今晚  他主动要求侍奉这桌
But tonight, he asked for this table.
是吗
Did he?
今晚的主题是「国境以南」
The theme of this evening is "South of the Border."
没错
Yes.
那么是谁为这些服务生选择了弗拉明戈舞的服装
So, who chose the flamenco outfits for the waiters?
我选的  怎么了
I did. Why?
弗拉明戈舞是西班牙的
Flamenco is Spanish.
南边那些国家不是说西班牙语的吗
Isn't that what they speak down there?
西班牙的  意思是在西班牙
Spanish, as in Spain.
是  但那也算国境以南
Yes, but it still counts as south of the border.
是啊  除非你指的是法国国境
Yes, if the border is with France.
你瞧我每天得忍受多么较真的一个人了吧
Oh, do you see what I have to live with?
自以为无所不知
Such a know-it-all.
是啊  我真是鄙视我渊博的知识
Yes, I'm forever flouting my knowledge
竟然知道西班牙在欧洲
that Spain is in Europe.
娜奥米  我想说
Naomi, can I just say
你儿子出落得如此英俊帅气  简直令我惊叹
I'm stunned at how handsome your son's become.
他穿着这种裤子还能呼吸  我也很震惊
I'm stunned he can breathe in those pants.
卡尔
Karl...
你让汤米有些不适了
you're making Tommy uncomfortable.
我吗  把他打扮成像丽莎·明尼利的
Me? I'm not the one who dressed him up
伴舞人员的人可不是我
as a backup dancer to Liza Minnelli.
再来一杯威士忌吧  年轻人
Another scotch, please, young man.
好的  格罗夫先生
Yes, Mr. Grove.
很好  谢谢
Very good. Thank you.
快点回来  汤米
Hurry back, Tommy.
你敢相信她竟然这样跟我儿子调情吗
Can you believe how she's flirting with my son?
桑迪只是闹着玩而已
Oh, Sandy is just being playful.
他才18岁  而她已经32岁了
He's 18. She's 32.
你不觉得那很可悲吗
Don't you think that's pathetic?
失陪下
Excuse me.
伏特加加冰  谢谢
Vodka rocks, please.
你得换一桌侍奉
You have to switch tables.
我做不到
I can't.
那就别老是盯着卡尔了
Then at least stop glaring at Karl.
他是个大混蛋
He's such a jerk.
他只是想显得风趣而已
He's just trying to be funny.
他在侮辱你的尊严
He's insulting your dignity.
你穿着这种衣服  没资格说这种话
You can't say that in those sleeves.
伏特加加冰
Ah, vodka rocks.
谢谢
Thank you.
你找到你的人生使命了
You've found your calling.
你在这儿啊
There you are.
-我在这儿  -你怎么没去跳舞
- Here I are. - Why aren't you dancing?
我好累
I'm tired.
-你准备好走了吗  -现在吗
- Are you about ready to go? - Now?
-是啊  -我跟薇沙玩得正开心呢
- Yeah. - I'm having so much fun with Wischa.
已经过了午夜了
Well, it's after midnight,
我明天还得早起  去工作
and I got to be up early and go to my job
需要我  穿正装  所以...
that requires me to, you know, wear clothes, so...
你喝了多少酒啊
How many of those have you had?
几杯
A couple.
可能不止吧
Maybe two couples.
你似乎很生气
You seem angry.
我没有生气
I'm not angry.
除非你打算跟这些低配版的名媛一起去威尼斯
Unless you're going to Venice with those low-rent Kardashians.
泰勒  说话客气点
Taylor, be nice.
他们是我的朋友
Those are my friends.
是啊  我只是一个将你从施暴的感情关系中
Yeah, and I'm just the person who saved you
解救出来  还让你住在我家的陌路人
from an abusive relationship and let you live in my house,
我他妈算哪颗葱  对吧
but fuck me, right?
好了  我觉得或许你该回家了
Okay. Um, I think maybe you should go home,
我会...
and I will...
-我们回头再见  -好吧
- I'll see you later. - Okay.
-好吗  -好啊
- Okay? - Yeah.
你要去威尼斯吗
Are you going to Venice?
我还不知道呢
I don't know yet.
好吧  去吧
Fine. Go!
祝你玩得开心
Have the best time.
-走吧  -什么  现在吗
- Come on. - What? Now?
-对  就现在  -好吧
- Yeah, now. - Okay.
斯坦顿家
Stanton residence.
宝贝  谢天谢地你在
Honey, thank God you're there.
罗伯
Rob.
你听起来很不安
You sound upset.
听着  之前你在我办公室的时候
Listen, when you were in my office earlier,
你有没有动过什么文件
did you happen to move any papers?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
德尔福项目的最终草案
The final draft of the Delphi Project.
之前就在我桌上现在不见了
It was here on my desk and now it's gone.
你找了桌子下面吗
Did you look under your desk?
找了  我哪里都找了
Yes, I've looked everywhere.
这非常重要
Now, this is incredibly important.
你确定你没动过吗
Are you sure you didn't touch it?
我很清楚不该碰你的东西
I know better than to touch your things.
该死
Damn it.
如果我找不到它我就要加班重做了
If I don't find this thing, I'll have to stay late and redo it,
全部他妈重做一遍
the whole goddamn thing.
你不是无论如何都会加班吗
I thought you were working late anyway.
那不是一回事
Uh... that was on something else.
那不重要  我得挂了  我得挂了
It doesn't matter. I have to go. I-I have to go.
德尔福项目
-你好  -你好  我找希拉
- Yeah? - Hi, I'd like to speak to Sheila.
我就是  你是谁
You're talking to her. Who's this?
我是说你的室友  另一个希拉
I think I mean your roommate, the other Sheila.
我是餐厅的艾普尔
Um, this is April from the diner.
天啊  好吧  等等
Oh, uh, Jesus, all right, hold on.
你知道是谁
You-know-who
她打电话来了  找你的
is on the phone. She wants to talk to you.
就知道她会打来的
Hm. I thought she might.
艾普尔
April?
嗨  我知道通知得有点晚
Hi. I know this is late notice,
但是今晚你愿意和我去夜店吗
but would you like to come with me to the club tonight?
罗伯放了我鸽子
Rob cancelled on me.
我现在一团糟  但是
I'm a mess right now, but
我猜我可以简单打扮一下
I guess I could throw myself together.
那太好了
Oh, good.
是伯班克的白钻石俱乐部
It's the White Diamond Bar in Burbank.
一个小时后我在那见你
I'll meet you there in an hour.
到时见
I'll be there.
-怎么了  -放尊重点  孩子们
- What's going on? - Show some respect, kids.
你们可是站在伟人面前
You're in the presence of greatness.
小心点大伙儿
Careful, everybody.
这些盘子很烫
These bowls are hot.
墨西哥酸辣汤
Tortilla soup.
你不能说这不是"国境以南"的菜肴了
You can't say this isn't "South of the Border."
鉴于萨蒙妮的地理水平
Given Simone's grasp of geography,
我很惊讶我们没喝蛤蜊汤
I'm surprised we're not having clam chowder.
顺便提一下
By the way,
你们听说拉里和苏的最新消息了吗
have you all heard the latest news about Larry and Sue?
他们怎么了
What about them?
他们分居了
They've separated.
-不会吧  -用这么惊讶吗
- No! - Are you really that surprised?
他们老是吵架
They fought constantly.
在我那个年代  人们通常会选择继续在一起
In my day, people stayed married
然后找到解决问题的办法
and found a way to work things out.
这方法不总是可行的
Well, that's not always possible.
萨蒙妮是对的
Simone's right.
人们可以深深关切对方
People can care deeply for one another,
但并不总是意味着他们需要一直做夫妻
it doesn't always mean that they should stay married.
你看  所以承诺才至关重要
You see, this is where I think commitment becomes essential.
人都会犯错
Everyone makes mistakes,
但是如果有爱在
but if love is there,
那就还有救赎之路可以走
then there's a path to redemption.
站着说话不腰疼
Easy for you to say.
你和萨蒙妮有着完美的婚姻
You and Simone have the perfect marriage.
很难说
Oh, hardly.
有时萨蒙妮会后悔嫁给我
There are days when Simone regrets marrying me.
我说得对吗  亲爱的
Am I right, my darling?
-后悔的时候多着去了  -对  我想象她在梦中
- More than a few. - Yes, I imagine she dreams
用枕头闷死我
of stifling me with a pillow
或者把我像旧鞋一样扔掉
or casting me aside like an old shoe.
宝贝  你知道我从来不扔鞋子的
Oh, honey, you know I'd never throw away a shoe.
但你不会如此轻易摆脱我的
But you don't get rid of me that easily.
你们看  她在婚姻殿堂里把手交给了我
You see, she gave me her hand in marriage.
-卡尔  -我知道你永远不会放手的
- Karl... - And I'm never going to let it go.
真该死
Bloody hell!
汤米  你怎么笨手笨脚的
Tommy, how could you be so clumsy?
抱歉  格罗夫先生
Sorry, Mr. Grove.
我给您拿些餐巾纸
Let me get you some napkins.
很显然他是故意的
Clearly, he did that on purpose.
不是  他只是没注意而已
No, he just wasn't paying attention.
你知道青少年是怎样的
You know how teenagers are.
好了  清醒的人啊  到家了
Okay, sober person, here we go.
把外套给我
Give me this.
停下  伊莱  别催我
Stop. Hey. Eli, don't rush me.
我没催你
I'm not rushing you.
你知道吗  我不明白
You know what? I don't get it.
怎么了  你不明白什么
What's that? What don't you get?
我不明白洁德在这些人身上看到了什么
I don't get what Jade sees in those people.
-薇沙  -对
- Wischa? - Yeah.
他们假死了
They're fake as shit.
是的  好了  抬腿脱裤子
Yes, they are. Okay, legs, pants.
你知道吗
And you know what?
为什么有人想看他们穿内衣的样子
Why would anyone want to see them in their underwear?
因为他们根本不好看
'Cause they're not even that pretty.
你认为他们好看吗
Do you think they're pretty?
只有他们的身体和脸好看
Only their bodies and their faces.
而现在洁德要和他们一起去威尼斯
And now Jade's going with them to Venice?
去她妈的
Fuck her.
有什么好笑的
What's funny?
你  你很好笑  因为你喝醉了在胡闹
You. You're funny 'cause you're drunk and ridiculous,
这是一个不错的角色互换
and that's a nice change of pace.
怎么说
From what?
这个嘛  当我做傻事的时候通常
Well, usually you're the one taking care of me
都是你照顾我
when I'm doing something stupid.
-我确实照顾你  -没错
- I do take care of you. - Yes, you do.
-我照顾所有人  -好的
- I take care of everybody. - Okay.
明早别内疚  好吗
Hey, don't feel bad in the morning, okay?
我为什么要内疚
Why would I feel bad?
因为你会记起自己对洁德有多粗鲁
'Cause you'll remember how rude you were to Jade.
别担心  她会原谅你
Don't worry, she'll forgive you.
去你的
Mm, fuck you.
我也会
And so will I.
我真开心你来了  你美呆了
I am so happy you came. You look amazing.
谢谢你邀请我
It was very kind for you to invite me.
我从没来过这样的地方
I never go to places like this.
如果你不来  我就得待在家里
Well, if you hadn't come, I would've had to stay home,
那有什么意思呢
and where is the fun in that?
真遗憾你的男人不能来
It's a shame your fella couldn't make it.
嗯  他说自己要加班  谁知道呢
Yeah, he said he had to work late, but who knows?
出轨的已婚男人
Married men who cheat
撒谎技术也一流
also know how to lie.
这肯定令人难过
It must be frustrating.
不知道罗伯是否会为妻子爽你的约
Never knowing if Rob is going to stand you up for his wife.
确实有些烦人
It can be annoying,
但这是交易
but it's a trade-off.
那你从中得到什么好处
So what do you get out of the deal?
自由
Freedom.
你瞧  我不想结婚
See, I don't want to get married.
所以这只是
So this is just a...
随便玩玩
casual fling?
对  等我玩够了罗伯的妻子会得回他
Yeah. Rob's wife will get him back when I'm done with him,
完好如初
good as new.
如果他继续加班
And if he keeps working late,
那就是一两周的事儿
it's going to be in a couple of weeks.
厉害  你真行
Oh, good. For you.
我是说  真有你的
I mean, good for you.
我们的服务生呢
Where is our waiter?
那艾普尔  你为什么不想结婚
So, April, why don't you want to get married?
因为我想发展事业
Because I want to have a career.
做什么
Doing what?
我想做个歌手
I want to be a singer.
真的吗
Really?
所以我想来这里
That's kind of why I wanted to come here.
周末这里让女孩伴唱
They have girls that sing with the combo on the weekends,
我打算向经理毛遂自荐
so I'm gonna introduce myself to the manager,
然后
and then
我会给他试唱
I am going to audition for him.
我都不知道你会唱歌
I had no idea you sang.
我以前是家乡教堂唱诗班的
I started in the church choir back at home.
父老乡亲都觉得我很有才华
Folks there think I'm pretty talented.
有一天我会出人头地
I'm gonna be somebody someday.
你看着吧
You just watch.
我喜欢音乐
I love music.
我以前弹钢琴
I used to play the piano.
真的假的
No kidding.
嗯  我学了很多年
Yeah, I took lessons for years.
你还弹吗
Well, do you still play?
事实上
The truth is,
我丈夫不喜欢我弹琴
my husband didn't care for my playing.
我犯傻告诉他我想举行演奏会
I made the mistake of telling him I wanted to give a recital,
他嘲笑了我
and he just laughed.
他说我没有自己想象的那么厉害
He said I wasn't as good as I thought I was.
这打消了我的热情
That sort of took the wind out of my sail.
亲爱的
Oh, honey.
你丈夫死了
Your husband's dead.
你不觉得该停止听他的话吗
Don't you think it's time you stopped listening to him?
今晚来这我真的很开心
Can I just say I am very happy to be here tonight?
敬我们
Well, here's to us.
泰勒  你干什么
Taylor, what are you doing?
你说得对  我得去找洁德
You were right. I have to go find Jade.
现在凌晨4点
It's 4:00 in the morning.
我就是个贱人  现在她要去威尼斯
I was such a bitch, and now she's going to Venice,
这都是我的错  我得弥补
and it's all my fault, and I have to fix this.
行  但你都不知道她在哪
All right, well, you don't even know where she is.
我知道  好吗  她在他们的酒店
Yes, I do, okay? I-I... She's at their hotel.
-你怎么知道  -我在她手机上装了"找我朋友"
- How do you know that? - I put Find My Friends on her phone.
-你在追踪她  -我得走了
- You're tracking her? - I got to go.
我的天
Oh, my God.
你是中了什么邪
Hey, what the fuck has gotten into you?
我不能失去她
I can't lose her.
你可以等她回来再和她谈
Well, you can wait until she gets home to talk to her.
如果她不回来呢
What if she doesn't come back?
如果她已经坐上去威尼斯的飞机
What if she's already on a plane to Venice
我再也见不到她了呢
and I never see her again?
你刚说她在酒店
You just said she's at the hotel.
我需要她
I need her.
如果她走了  一切都会支离破碎
If she leaves, this whole fucking thing falls apart.
不
No...
不行
No.
停车
Stop the car.
这是什么意思
What does that mean?
一切都支离破碎
What whole thing falls apart?
伊莱  下去
Eli, get off.
不  你得给我出来
No, you're gonna get out
现在跟我谈谈  泰勒
and you're gonna talk to me right now, taylor.
真的吗
Really?
跟我谈谈  泰勒
Just talk to me, Taylor.
怎么了
What's going on?
拜托
Come on.
我之前问过你是否爱上她了
I asked you before if you were in love with her.
我知道  我知道
I-I know, I know.
-你骗了我  -也不是
- You lied to me. - Not exactly.
那我们在这儿干什么
Then what the hell are we doing in the driveway?
伊莱  拜托  求你了
Eli, come on, please.
这  这太艰难了
This is, this is too hard!
-什么  -我不知道
- What? - I-I don't know.
-什么事  -我的生活  我的生活太艰难了
- What? - My life, my l... my life is so hard!
我每天要工作那么久  接的案子又糟心
I-I... The hours I work, the cases I take.
然后回到这个房子
And then I come home to this house.
这个我们负担不起的大房子
This big, fucking house that we can't afford!
房贷的钱得我出
And I have to pay for it
因为你已经有两年没卖出过剧本了
because you haven't sold a script in two years.
但我不能提起这事
But I can't bring that up
不然我就成了坏人了
because then I'm a bitch.
所以我绝口不提
So I say nothing.
而洁德是我生活里唯一轻松的事
And Jade is the only thing in my life that is easy.
因为她不索取
'Cause she doesn't take.
她只给予
She only gives.
如果她离开  我不知道我会怎么做
If she leaves, I don't know what I'm gonna do.
你怎么不早点跟我说这些
Why didn't you tell me any of this before?
拜托
Come on.
我不想伤害你
I don't want to hurt you.
好明智的决定
Oh, well, great call.
因为你伤到我了
'Cause it hurts.
那...
So, I mean...
你想我走吗
Do you want me to go?
不
No.
伊莱  我爱你
Eli, I love you.
但你想让她留下
But you want her to stay.
我
I mean...
这样要怎么成
How does that even work?
我不知道
I don't know.
真的
I don't.
但必须成
But it has to.
不然跟我做夫妻太难了
Because otherwise, it's just too hard to be married to me.
不  伊莱
No. Eli...
我被炒了
I got fired.
一点不意外  你的行为太幼稚了
I'm not surprised. What you did was childish.
-他当时抓着你  -他是握着我的手
- He was grabbing you. - He was holding my hand.
-你为什么一直帮他说话  -我没有
- Why do you keep defending him? - I'm not.
他骗了你  背着你出轨
He's lied to you, he's cheated on you
还不肯离开你家
and he won't leave your home.
情况太复杂了
The situation is complicated.
是啊  因为根本不合逻辑
Well, yeah, it must be, because it makes no sense.
-你应该恨他  -我知道  只是
- You should hate him. - I know, I know, it's just...
他是我丈夫
He's my husband.
他忍受我的奢侈和无理取闹
He puts up with my extravagance and my nonsense.
他会在我最需要赞美的时候夸我漂亮
He tells me I'm beautiful when I need to hear it the most and...
他可以用独一无二的方式逗我笑
he makes me laugh in a way that no one else can.
萨蒙妮
Simone...
我总有一天会和卡尔离婚的
One day, I will divorce Karl,
但我永远不会恨他
but I will never hate him,
因为我做不到
because I can't.
那我怎么办
Where does that leave me?
在餐车上
In the back of a van
度过欢愉时光
having a marvelous time.
餐车是公司配的
Yeah, well, van came with the job, so...
别担心
Don't worry.
我们会想办法解决的
We'll figure it out.
格罗夫太太
Mrs. Grove.
哈特夫人说该你们表演了
Mrs. Harte says it's time for your number.
谢谢
Thank you.
我得走了
I have to go.
那个  关于今晚  我很抱歉
Listen, about tonight, I'm so sorry.
-你不必道歉  -不  有必要
- You don't have to apologize. - No, I do.
真的
I really do.
谢谢
Thank you.
我决定和米沙还有薇珞去威尼斯
So, I decided to go to Venice with Mischa and Willow.
是时候了
It's time.
跟你和伊莱生活在一起
Being here with you and Eli, it's...
这里让我几乎有了家的感觉
...starting to feel like a home.
我产生了感情
I'm getting attached.
最后我总是会受伤
Which always leads to me getting hurt.
在结束的时候
When it ends. So...
我应该离开
I should go.
如果不需要结束呢
What if it doesn't have to end?
如果你能留下呢
What if you stayed?
如果这就是你家呢
What if this was your home?
把这当做你家
Here with us.
你什么意思
What are you saying?
和我们一起生活
Live with us.
跟我们在一起
Be with us.
对
Yeah.
没理由离开
There's no reason to leave.
你才刚回家
You just got home.
嗨
Hi.
你还没睡
Oh, you're still up.
当然
Of course.
你搞定工作了吗
Did you get your work finished?
嗯
Yep.
我重新做了整个项目  花了好久
I redid the whole project. It took forever.
你想的话我可以给你做点心
I could fix you a snack if you like.
不用  我去弄杯马天尼  然后洗个澡
No. I'm gonna make myself a martini, take a shower
就睡觉
and go to bed.
好
All right.
我弹会儿钢琴可以吗
Would it bother you if I played the piano for a bit?
已经过了午夜了
It's after midnight.
我知道  如果你介意的话...
I know. If you'd rather I didn't...
不  你想弹就弹吧
Nah. Whatever you want.
亲爱的  我的马天尼需要橄榄
Honey, I need an olive for my martini.
看看冰箱
Check the fridge.
-找不到橄榄  -最上面
- I can't find the olives. - Top shelf.
我找了  不在
I checked. They weren't there.
再找找
Check again.
亲爱的
Honey!
没有橄榄
It's not really a martini
就算不上是马天尼
without an olive.
谢谢  你知道
Thanks. You know,
很晚了
it is so late.
我们该去睡了
We should turn in.